Guide to the
Brown University Library
- MNGW 1st Printing Errata.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Date created: 2013-05-04 16:38:42 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-05-04 17:21:26 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 2 kb pass 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Attic/Date created: 2011-08-07 15:22:53 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-07 23:59:07 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3 MNGW Chapter 3 KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-06-29 23:40:18 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-01 20:47:37 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Rogue femininity.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Beth Marston/Date created: 2010-09-03 19:04:50 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-09-03 19:04:50 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- turn around damn door.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/6/7/1/Attachments/176915/3/Date created: 2015-10-03 13:53:36 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-03 13:53:36 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 2-4.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/~~ First Draft ~~/Date created: 2009-09-22 14:06:52 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-09-25 16:47:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW chapter 9 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 9/Date created: 2012-07-05 17:48:29 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-05 17:48:59 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- BC_UT_Sweden_4_Berliners.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/7/8/1/Attachments/187092/2.4/Date created: 2015-10-22 19:56:36 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-22 19:56:36 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Blank.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/57F6CF73-8A8B-4A58-8154-FFD84FE00244/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/0/9/1/Attachments/190847/2/Date created: 2015-10-22 19:56:10 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-22 19:56:10 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- DixonPlaceQPDlaunchFlier.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Dixon Place Launch/Date created: 2012-04-16 22:45:16 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-18 22:14:08 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-5 Girl.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/~~ First Draft ~~/Date created: 2011-07-11 15:31:41 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-07-19 15:46:00 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- New Gigs 09 outline.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/Date created: 2009-01-20 18:15:53 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-01-20 21:12:11 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Book 2 Exported From Scrivener.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Attic/Book Two IP/Date created: 2011-08-07 15:29:32 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-07 15:30:52 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Scientology Nuts and Bolts.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Scientology ƒ/Date created: 2009-02-06 12:02:57 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-06 15:07:14 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kate at the hospital.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/kb-health to 2012/Date created: 2008-06-12 00:32:29 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-06-06 13:25:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB long bio May 2015 pages09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2016-01-31 16:17:16 EST-0500Date modified: 2016-01-31 16:17:16 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- call me a cockeyed optimist.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Scientology ƒ/Scientology Piece/Date created: 2008-02-06 10:38:58 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-14 13:59:39 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- A Queer And Pleasant Danger.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/QPD-The Real Deal/Date created: 2011-11-14 17:12:25 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-11-22 09:47:01 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Limericks copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Date created: 2012-07-03 19:47:35 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-03 19:47:35 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- book 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/for alan/Date created: 2011-09-07 15:08:26 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-07 15:08:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- There and Back Again.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/4/8/1/Attachments/184651/1/Date created: 2015-10-23 12:04:40 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-23 12:04:40 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- My Girlfriend Is Becoming The Man Of My Dreams.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/people in my life/Date created: 2011-05-17 23:01:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-18 00:05:23 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 10 KB Edit Chap 10.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/Date created: 2013-01-18 13:34:49 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-19 13:22:12 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2016-01-24 20:54:47 EST-0500Date modified: 2016-01-24 20:54:47 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Power Bottoming panel at TES.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/TES Power Bottoming Panel/Date created: 2009-05-19 23:47:25 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-05-21 20:08:34 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dixon Place QPD Launch Schedule.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Dixon Place Launch/Date created: 2012-04-30 12:38:10 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-30 12:38:10 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- eulogy for my brother.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Alan Eulogy/Date created: 2009-01-01 12:33:16 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-01-11 19:26:37 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- New BDSM Chapter—KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2017-04-03 12:48:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-04-03 12:48:45 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- QueerPleasantDanger1_5.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/scripts/Queer&Pleasant Solo Show/Date created: 2010-11-21 15:07:39 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-11-21 15:07:39 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- FM-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~~Copy Editing QPD~~/Date created: 2011-10-26 14:07:28 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-10-28 15:14:09 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Good Sportsmen.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Itty Bitty Archive/Brown Anthology/Date created: 2013-05-05 13:23:23 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-05-05 13:23:24 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Kyriarchy Worksheer 2-up.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 3 Let X = X/Date created: 2012-02-07 18:05:26 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-11 15:15:10 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Beautiful Girls.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Itty Bitty Archive/Brown Anthology/Date created: 2013-05-05 17:17:20 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-05-05 17:20:45 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Keynote Champaign-Urbana Pride Festival.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Utah Pride QvS/Keynote Champaign-Urbana Pride Festival/Date created: 2013-08-26 12:32:44 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-09-07 10:25:18 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- betsey_girls_saved_my_life.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Articles to Mine for MNGW/Journals/Betsey Girls/Date created: 2010-01-15 19:04:58 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-15 19:04:58 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-2 Borderline ƒ/Date created: 2011-01-06 15:31:03 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-01-13 22:49:14 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Bornstein QAF contract 2012.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Vancouver Queer Arts Festival 2012/Date created: 2012-07-10 14:44:44 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-10 14:46:41 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Talking Points B's Ecstasy Hour.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/AV & Keynote Docs/Hello Cruel Workshop/Date created: 2012-08-28 15:33:09 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-28 17:27:39 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires 2013.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2013-09-18 23:29:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-09-20 02:03:59 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- dixon place femme blurb.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2011-05-10 18:57:58 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-10 18:57:58 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 09-10 newsletter.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Newsletters/09-10 Newsletter Folder/Date created: 2009-08-18 14:55:09 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-08-19 21:22:59 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Bornstein_letter_4_John_Emigh.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Date created: 2009-01-28 19:47:58 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-01-29 14:08:37 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Trans Survey Draft #2 KB pass pages 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2016-01-25 20:29:38 EST-0500Date modified: 2016-01-25 20:29:38 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kate at the hospital.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Date created: 2008-06-12 00:32:29 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-06-06 13:25:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Letter to Media Galley Readers.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Blurber Letters/Date created: 2012-01-13 00:03:24 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-13 13:52:25 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Crossed Genres.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Crossed Genres/Date created: 2010-08-05 19:35:31 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-05 19:35:31 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 2 MNGW Chapter 2 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 2 Where Is Gender?/Date created: 2012-07-14 17:06:06 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-14 17:07:01 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Family Man copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/ Book 2, Chapter 4/Date created: 2009-01-17 11:44:57 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-03 16:34:01 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Book 2 Chapter 5 - 3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 2 Chap 5/Date created: 2009-12-29 10:43:56 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-12-29 18:58:03 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MWRU Performance Script 2017 BC copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/57F6CF73-8A8B-4A58-8154-FFD84FE00244/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/9/6/3/Attachments/369953/1/Date created: 2017-04-15 15:13:20 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-04-15 15:13:20 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- IRS Payment Letter Jul-Aug 2011 copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/IRS Payment Agreement/Monthly Payments to IRS/Date created: 2011-08-30 11:38:52 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-30 11:38:52 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- A Plan For Peace Nov 27 92.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/culture watch/Sex and SM/Date created: 2011-05-17 23:15:35 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-17 23:15:35 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- william paterson piece.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Beyond Red or Blue/Date created: 2008-09-22 10:50:54 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-02-28 14:33:56 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Gender Is A Caterpillar Introduction.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw China/Date created: 2013-08-06 15:44:39 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-08-06 15:51:31 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- hcw1pg.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Hello Cruel World/Date created: 2010-03-09 12:04:58 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-03-09 12:04:58 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- turn around damn door.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/New York Living/Date created: 2011-08-28 11:56:37 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-28 12:04:06 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- GASP 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/GASP/Date created: 2012-02-24 15:41:57 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-03-23 01:05:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Tao of Mitzvah Sabbath Boddhisatva.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Articles to Mine for MNGW/Date created: 2010-02-02 16:34:37 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-02-02 16:34:38 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Talking Points Pre-Trans March.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Pride/Toronto Trans Pride 2011/Date created: 2011-07-01 12:16:37 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-07-01 12:26:54 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- exercise—coalition building.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 10/Date created: 2012-06-27 12:22:28 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-27 12:22:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Ernie 98 card.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Pictures/Graphic Work In Progress/98 Card for Ernie/Date created: 2013-02-18 16:51:29 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-02-18 16:51:29 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- BC to Donia Finders Fees Smackdown.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2013-02-08 13:33:56 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-02-09 00:01:57 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- LuMi_2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-02-08 17:43:06 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-02-08 17:43:06 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Old Chapter 8 Beta.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 9/Date created: 2012-04-12 12:36:17 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-13 20:25:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb_medical_history_2010.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Date created: 2010-07-15 20:22:50 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-07-15 20:30:18 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KateBornsteinRebelCupcake.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Crossed Genres/Date created: 2010-09-02 18:46:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-09-02 18:46:57 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Inherit the Earth notebook notes.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Inherit The Earth/Inherit the Wind Attic/Date created: 2009-06-06 13:12:33 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-06-06 13:12:33 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- cheap sex with bc.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/BC this and that/Date created: 2009-02-02 17:25:37 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-03 20:10:34 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- IRS Payment Letter Feb 2012.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/IRS Payment Agreement/Monthly Payments to IRS/Date created: 2012-02-13 10:09:51 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-13 11:59:55 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2009-02-18 09:53:46 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-11-19 12:14:32 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Description.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Archive Project/Date created: 2011-05-23 15:11:21 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-23 15:11:21 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- FM-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~~Copy Editing QPD~~/Date created: 2011-10-18 12:27:14 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-10-28 14:50:42 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Questions_for_Switzerland BC Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2013-04-17 14:07:59 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-04-17 14:16:55 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 3 KB pass 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Book Three/Date created: 2011-08-19 12:20:08 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-19 12:49:49 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Virtually Yours Intro, Beta 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/scripts/Virtually Yours ƒ/Date created: 2011-05-22 16:35:52 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-22 17:34:39 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- China Film Text 1st Draft P09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/China Film/Date created: 2013-11-08 20:51:29 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-11-08 20:51:29 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 2 (original).pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Attic/Date created: 2011-08-05 16:08:56 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-06 14:24:03 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Seasonal_8.5x11.AddressLabel_centered_6-2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Pictures/Graphic Work In Progress/2009 Xmas Journal Collage/Date created: 2009-12-20 14:37:06 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-12-20 14:54:09 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Queer and Pleasant Danger Part 3 KB pass 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Book Three/Date created: 2011-08-30 19:27:53 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-31 13:18:06 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- GOTNG Triangle Publishing Prize Acceptance Talk.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/GOTNG Triangle Publishing Award/Date created: 2011-04-28 15:57:09 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-02 09:54:13 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Please Read Me First.pages